mnrdaily.com 2018-02-25

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy applies to the Web site only and does not cover information collected on any third-party sites to which this Web site links. This privacy policy is part of, and must be read in conjunction with, the Web site's Terms and Conditions. You can read the entire Terms and Conditions by either scrolling up to the top of this Web page or by clicking here. If you do not agree with the Terms and Conditions in their entirety, please do not use this Web site.

##### Web Site Users

The Web site generally collects personally identifiable information such as a name, postal address, E-mail address, telephone number, or credit card information with your specific knowledge and consent.

##### How does the Web site use information supplied by me?

Occasionally, visitors to our Web site may be asked to supply certain personally identifying information, which is then retained by the Web site. For example, we ask you for certain information if you choose to subscribe to our E-mail newsletters, register with our online discussion forums, or purchase either articles from our archives or our premium online content. If you choose to give us personally identifying information at such time, such information will be retained by us and used only to provide you with products or services you have requested, or with additional information from the Web site, its affiliates, or selected outside companies whose products or services we feel may be of use to you. Any information from selected outside companies will be transmitted by the Web site so that such companies will not have access either to your E-mail address or to your other personally identifying information. Moreover, we will not sell or rent any personally identifying information obtained through the Web site to any other company or organization.

If, at some point after giving the Web site your personally identifying information, you do not wish to continue to receive additional information from the Web site, its affiliates, or selected outside companies, in general, you may opt out by submitting a request via our Contact Us page with the words "remove my name" in the subject line of your E-mail; in the case of our E-mail newsletters, you also may follow the procedures at our E-mail newsletter registration page.

From time to time, the personally identifying information that you provide to us may be shared with our suppliers or service providers who assist us in maintaining and managing our newsletters, our archives, our premium online content, our online discussion forums, and other activities on the Web site. Such suppliers or service providers may use your personally identifying information only in the course of providing services to the Web site, but they may not use such information for other purposes.

While your individual information is protected as discussed above, the Web site reserves the right to use such individual information to create aggregated, anonymous data about users in order to develop statistics about activity on and visitors to the Web site. In addition, the Web site may disclose personal information if we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Web site; or (4) protect the personal safety, property, or rights of our users or the public.

##### What are "cookies" and how do you use them?

"Cookies" are pieces of information that are placed by a Web site in a storage place on your computer. Cookies do not contain information that is, in itself, personally identifying. The Web site places cookies on your computer in a limited way to help deliver advertisements, to calculate unique site visitors, and to track usage throughout our site. Other uses include placement of cookies to make the login process more convenient for users of our E-mail newsletters, our archives, our premium online content, and our online discussion forums. In addition, some advertisers may place cookies on your computer. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers.

##### How is my credit card information used when I make a purchase?

When you make a purchase, we ask you to provide your credit card information so that we can process your payment. During the ordering process, such credit card information is transmitted to the Web site (in the case of our premium online content) or (in the case of our archives, subscriptions, and mail order products) to one of our suppliers or service providers. In both cases, credit card information is then transmitted to third-party credit card processors and card issuers that must use your information to process your order.

##### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

No one under the age of 13 should provide any personal information. In general, the Web site does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If in limited circumstances we do knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, we will do so only with verified parental consent prior to collection. In the event that we learn that we have collected information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete this information from our database as quickly as possible. If you believe the Web site has any information about anyone under 13, please contact us via our Contact Us page.

##### About Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>
